[{"answer": " Britta, Ive been thinking about visiting China to see the Olympics.  What do yo", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " That sounds great like a good idea.  I really wanted to go see the Summe", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Britta, Ive been thinking about visiting China to see the Olympics.  What do yo", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Well, we have money now, but how do we get tickets", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 23, "question": " That sounds great like a good idea.  I really wanted to go see the Summe", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " I bet we can find something about it online.  Maybe we can purchase ticket", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well, we have money now, but how do we get tickets", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " This is exciting!  What events should we go see", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " I bet we can find something about it online.  Maybe we can purchase ticket", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Hmm, I remember when the torch bearer ran through our city in 1996", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 29, "question": " This is exciting!  What events should we go see", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Oh, are you talking about the relay of the Olympic torch", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Hmm, I remember when the torch bearer ran through our city in 1996", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Yeah.  All the modern Olympic Games now have torch relays.  They first light th", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Oh, are you talking about the relay of the Olympic torch", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I remember too.  They just chose some important people from our community t", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Yeah.  All the modern Olympic Games now have torch relays.  They first light th", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " For the 2008 Olympics, the torch is going through San Francisco, but it won", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I remember too.  They just chose some important people from our community t", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Well, we cant buy tickets to go see the torch relay.  Thats not an event.  We ca", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " For the 2008 Olympics, the torch is going through San Francisco, but it won", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Yep.  Do you remember who did it in Atlanta", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Well, we cant buy tickets to go see the torch relay.  Thats not an event.  We ca", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Ummm.  It was that famous boxer.  Oh!  Mohammed Ali", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yep.  Do you remember who did it in Atlanta", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " So, how about we get tickets to the opening ceremony", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Ummm.  It was that famous boxer.  Oh!  Mohammed Ali", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Ok.  I think I found a website that will let us buy tickets.  Its all in Chinese!  Oh", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 57, "question": " So, how about we get tickets to the opening ceremony", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": "I guess there wont be too many available for us.  What kind of things do they d", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Ok.  I think I found a website that will let us buy tickets.  Its all in Chinese!  Oh", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " The opening ceremony is like a big show put on by the host city.  They usually d", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": "I guess there wont be too many available for us.  What kind of things do they d", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Isnt the opening ceremony the part where there is the big parade of all th", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 70, "question": " The opening ceremony is like a big show put on by the host city.  They usually d", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Yeah, all the athletes get in groups of their countries and carry their country", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Isnt the opening ceremony the part where there is the big parade of all th", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " So, how about those tickets", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Yeah, all the athletes get in groups of their countries and carry their country", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Uh, it looks like all the opening ceremony tickets are sold out.  Ill try the closin", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 80, "question": " So, how about those tickets", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Ok, I guess.  But, what happens in the closing ceremony?  All I know is that the", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Uh, it looks like all the opening ceremony tickets are sold out.  Ill try the closin", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Yes, they do that at the end.  Also, they exchange flags.  The host countr", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Ok, I guess.  But, what happens in the closing ceremony?  All I know is that the", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": "first tha", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Yes, they do that at the end.  Also, they exchange flags.  The host countr", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Oooh, I want to go see that.  How much are tickets", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 97, "question": "first tha", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Actually, theyre sold out.  Almost all the tickets that we can buy are sold out", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Oooh, I want to go see that.  How much are tickets", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Well, at least theyre not all sold out.  Whats left", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Actually, theyre sold out.  Almost all the tickets that we can buy are sold out", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " There are tickets left for womens handball", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Well, at least theyre not all sold out.  Whats left", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Womens handball!  Whats that?  Ive never heard of it", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 101, "question": " There are tickets left for womens handball", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Me neither.  I dont really want to see that.  I guess we can always try to bu", "docId": "08-08", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Womens handball!  Whats that?  Ive never heard of it", "qSentId": 101}]
